so the Bible speaks of this angel named
Lucifer he was the brightest and most
beautiful angel in all of heaven in fact
his name Lucifer means Light Bearer his
superpower in heaven was to reflect the
glory and beauty of God but this angel
sin he fell from heaven and I need you
to listen carefully because Lucifer did
not cease to be a library he is in fact
today still a light bearer but he is now
a false light bearer his superpower now
is to cause others to see in a false
light with false filters through false
lights
Lucifer calls one third of the angels in
heaven to be deceived and through false
lights Lucifer is deceiving many today
so I have a question for you do you see
yourself in a negative light do you see
yourself as worthless do you see your
future as bleak as Portus
people have struggled with the thought
of taking their lives because they have
been looking at themselves through the
false filters of the enemy we have
conflicts in our homes in our churches
in our communities in our world because
people are looking through false filters
this is why the Bible says let this mind
be in you which was also in Christ Jesus
because when the mind of Christ is in
you you see through his eyes and you
begin to realize just how important you
are just how much your worth is in the
sight of God you see the Bible says for
God so loved the world that He gave His
only begotten Son that whosoever
believeth in him should not perish but
have everlasting life when you realize
that Christ came to this world to die
for you you will begin to see just how
much you are worth in his eyes and just
how much others are worth in his eyes
so listen stop viewing yourself through
the false filters of the enemy let this
mind be in you which was also in Christ
Jesus and allow his light to shatter
Satan's
false picture of you be encouraged
you